eventstudytools.com 2018-12-24

# Data Policy | Event Study Tools

EventStudyTools.com is strongly commited to the privacy of your personal information. This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which EventStudyTools.com uses, maintains and discloses information collected from its customers and users of its website. You find our Swiss data privacy policy in German language further down this page.

**General Data Policy**  
EventStudyTools.com does not collect personal information. There is no login required (or even possible) to use this website or its services. If you should use a server-side program provided by EventStudyTools.com and upload CSV files as inputs for this program, no data included in these CSV will be stored beyond the time required to produce the requested results and allow the download of the analysis' results. All data will be cleared from the server's memory after a short period of time following the completion of the calculations implied by the requested analysis.

**What are Cookies?**  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. We may use both session ID cookies. For session ID cookies, once you close your browser, the cookie terminates and is erased. Session ID cookies may be used to track user preferences while the user is visiting the website. They also help to minimize load times and save on server processing. Cookies used on the EventStudyTools.com website do not contain personally identifiable information.

**Log Files**  
Like most standard websites, we use log files. This information may include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. However, none of the information stored in our log files, including but not limited to IP addresses, is linked to personally identifiable information.

**How we use this information**  
We use the presented information for research purposes regarding the effectiveness of our website services, marketing, advertising and sales efforts. EventStudyTools.com will not in any way share this information with a third party.

**Disclosure of Information**  
EventStudyTools.com may disclose information as it deems necessary, in its sole discretion, to: (a) comply with legal process or other legal requirements, including but not limited to responding to civil or criminal subpoenas, search warrants, national security letters, court orders, or other requests for information from law enforcement officials; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of EventStudyTools.com, agents, affiliates, licensees, and customers; or (c) carry out its obligations under or enforce this Agreement or to assign its rights under this Agreement.

EventStudyTools.com may from time to time engage third parties, including its own subsidiaries and affiliated companies, to preserve, analyze or otherwise store or process data received by EventStudyTools.com from its customers. Such third party service providers are required to treat all such data with the same degree of care as EventStudyTools.com and are prohibited from disclosing such data to any other person or party, except as otherwise provided for in this Privacy Policy.

EventStudyTools.com may also disclose aggregate, anonymous data based on information collected from users to investors and potential partners. In such cases, only statistical information will be disclosed. In case EventStudyTools.com is sold, the information collected from users may be transferred to the new owners.

**Legal Disclaimer**  
The EventStudyTools.com website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that EventStudyTools.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. The EventStudyTools.com Privacy Policy as described herein applies solely to information collected by EventStudyTools.com.

**Maintenance of Information**  
The information provided to EventStudyTools.com is saved indefinitely and may be stored on one or more databases directly or indirectly maintained by EventStudyTools.com. EventStudyTools.com employs industry-standard security measures to protect the confidentiality of the information. While we cannot guarantee that loss, misuse or alteration of data will not occur; we make every effort to prevent such occurrences.

**Advertisement**  
We use Google AdSense Advertising on our website. Google's advertising requirements can be summed up by Google's Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. [https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en. ](https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en.%C2%A0)Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on previous visits to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt-out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google Ad and Content Network privacy policy. We, along with third-party vendors such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.

Opting out:Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative Opt Out page or by using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.

**Encryption/SSL**  
For all sensitive actions, e.g. the purchase of a passey, the website switches to a secure connection. Secure connections are indicated by the padlock icon in fron of the domain and the 'http **s** ://'-prefix. Information transmitted to one of these secure pages is encrypted following high grade 256-bit encryption standards. The certificate is signed/verified by [www.GoDaddy.com](http://www.godaddy.com/), one of the world's leading SSL providers and web hosters. Please review the certificate's authenticity by clicking on the 'trust mark' at the very bottom of this page.

* * *

**Datenschutz**

Gestützt auf Artikel 13 der schweizerischen Bundesverfassung und die datenschutzrechtlichen Bestimmungen des Bundes (Datenschutzgesetz, DSG) hat jede Person Anspruch auf Schutz ihrer Privatsphäre sowie auf Schutz vor Missbrauch ihrer persönlichen Daten. Wir halten diese Bestimmungen ein. Persönliche Daten werden streng vertraulich behandelt und weder an Dritte verkauft noch weiter gegeben. In enger Zusammenarbeit mit unseren Hosting-Providern bemühen wir uns, die Datenbanken so gut wie möglich vor fremden Zugriffen, Verlusten, Missbrauch oder vor Fälschung zu schützen.

Beim Zugriff auf unsere Webseiten werden folgende Daten in Logfiles gespeichert: IP-Adresse, Datum, Uhrzeit, Browser-Anfrage und allg. übertragene Informationen zum Betriebssystem resp. Browser. Diese Nutzungsdaten bilden die Basis für statistische, anonyme Auswertungen, so dass Trends erkennbar sind, anhand derer wir unsere Angebote entsprechend verbessern können.

**Datenschutzerklärung für die Nutzung von Facebook-Plugins (Like-Button)**

Auf unseren Seiten sind Plugins des sozialen Netzwerks Facebook, 1601 South California Avenue, Palo Alto, CA 94304, USA integriert. Die Facebook-Plugins erkennen Sie an dem Facebook-Logo oder dem "Like-Button" ("Gefällt mir") auf unserer Seite. Eine Übersicht über die Facebook-Plugins finden Sie hier: <http://developers.facebook.com/docs/plugins/>.

Wenn Sie unsere Seiten besuchen, wird über das Plugin eine direkte Verbindung zwischen Ihrem Browser und dem Facebook-Server hergestellt. Facebook erhält dadurch die Information, dass Sie mit Ihrer IP-Adresse unsere Seite besucht haben. Wenn Sie den Facebook "Like-Button" anklicken während Sie in Ihrem Facebook-Account eingeloggt sind, können Sie die Inhalte unserer Seiten auf Ihrem Facebook-Profil verlinken. Dadurch kann Facebook den Besuch unserer Seiten Ihrem Benutzerkonto zuordnen. Wir weisen darauf hin, dass wir als Anbieter der Seiten keine Kenntnis vom Inhalt der übermittelten Daten sowie deren Nutzung durch Facebook erhalten. Weitere Informationen hierzu finden Sie in der Datenschutzerklärung von facebook unter <https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/>

Wenn Sie nicht wünschen, dass Facebook den Besuch unserer Seiten Ihrem Facebook-Nutzerkonto zuordnen kann, loggen Sie sich bitte aus Ihrem Facebook-Benutzerkonto aus.

**Datenschutzerklärung für die Nutzung von Twitter**

Auf unseren Seiten sind Funktionen des Dienstes Twitter eingebunden. Diese Funktionen werden angeboten durch die Twitter Inc., 795 Folsom St., Suite 600, San Francisco, CA 94107, USA. Durch das Benutzen von Twitter und der Funktion "Re-Tweet" werden die von Ihnen besuchten Webseiten mit Ihrem Twitter-Account verknüpft und anderen Nutzern bekannt gegeben. Dabei werden u.a. Daten wie IP-Adresse, Browsertyp, aufgerufene Domains, besuchte Seiten, Mobilfunkanbieter, Geräte- und Applikations-IDs und Suchbegriffe an Twitter übertragen.

Wir weisen darauf hin, dass wir als Anbieter der Seiten keine Kenntnis vom Inhalt der übermittelten Daten sowie deren Nutzung durch Twitter erhalten. Aufgrund laufender Aktualisierung der Datenschutzerklärung von Twitter, weisen wir auf die aktuellste Version unter (<http://twitter.com/privacy>) hin.

**Datenschutzerklärung für die Nutzung von Google Adsense**

Diese Website benutzt Google AdSense, einen Dienst zum Einbinden von Werbeanzeigen der Google Inc. ("Google"). Google AdSense verwendet sog. "Cookies", Textdateien, die auf Ihrem Computer gespeichert werden und die eine Analyse der Benutzung der Website ermöglicht. Google AdSense verwendet auch so genannte Web Beacons (unsichtbare Grafiken). Durch diese Web Beacons können Informationen wie der Besucherverkehr auf diesen Seiten ausgewertet werden.

Die durch Cookies und Web Beacons erzeugten Informationen über die Benutzung dieser Website (einschließlich Ihrer IP-Adresse) und Auslieferung von Werbeformaten werden an einen Server von Google in den USA übertragen und dort gespeichert. Diese Informationen können von Google an Vertragspartner von Google weiter gegeben werden. Google wird Ihre IP-Adresse jedoch nicht mit anderen von Ihnen gespeicherten Daten zusammenführen.

Sie können die Installation der Cookies durch eine entsprechende Einstellung Ihrer Browser Software verhindern; wir weisen Sie jedoch darauf hin, dass Sie in diesem Fall gegebenenfalls nicht sämtliche Funktionen dieser Website voll umfänglich nutzen können. Durch die Nutzung dieser Website erklären Sie sich mit der Bearbeitung der über Sie erhobenen Daten durch Google in der zuvor beschriebenen Art und Weise und zu dem zuvor benannten Zweck einverstanden.

**Datenschutzerklärung für die Nutzung von Google Analytics**

Diese Website benutzt Google Analytics, einen Webanalysedienst der Google Inc. ("Google"). Google Analytics verwendet sog. "Cookies", Textdateien, die auf Ihrem Computer gespeichert werden und die eine Analyse der Benutzung der Website durch Sie ermöglichen. Die durch den Cookie erzeugten Informationen über Ihre Benutzung dieser Website werden in der Regel an einen Server von Google in den USA übertragen und dort gespeichert. Im Falle der Aktivierung der IP-Anonymisierung auf dieser Webseite wird Ihre IP-Adresse von Google jedoch innerhalb von Mitgliedstaaten der Europäischen Union oder in anderen Vertragsstaaten des Abkommens über den Europäischen Wirtschaftsraum zuvor gekürzt.

Nur in Ausnahmefällen wird die volle IP-Adresse an einen Server von Google in den USA übertragen und dort gekürzt. Google wird diese Informationen benutzen, um Ihre Nutzung der Website auszuwerten, um Reports über die Websiteaktivitäten für die Websitebetreiber zusammenzustellen und um weitere mit der Websitenutzung und der Internetnutzung verbundene Dienstleistungen zu erbringen. Auch wird Google diese Informationen gegebenenfalls an Dritte übertragen, sofern dies gesetzlich vorgeschrieben oder soweit Dritte diese Daten im Auftrag von Google verarbeiten. Die im Rahmen von Google Analytics von Ihrem Browser übermittelte IP-Adresse wird nicht mit anderen Daten von Google zusammengeführt.

Sie können die Installation der Cookies durch eine entsprechende Einstellung Ihrer Browser Software verhindern; wir weisen Sie jedoch darauf hin, dass Sie in diesem Fall gegebenenfalls nicht sämtliche Funktionen dieser Website voll umfänglich nutzen können. Durch die Nutzung dieser Website erklären Sie sich mit der Bearbeitung der über Sie erhobenen Daten durch Google in der zuvor beschriebenen Art und Weise und zu dem zuvor benannten Zweck einverstanden.
